{"data":[{"question":"Mr Smith's office is_____ the second floor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"I saw Mrs Jones waiting_____ the bus stop.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"Gerhard has some nice pictures hanging ____ his office wall.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"I work____the city centre.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"Her office is____the end of the corridor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"My office is____the second floor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"Waiter, there's a fly____my soup.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"he cat sat____the mat.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"I was____hospital in March.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"},{"question":"His office is____the top of the stairs.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"2"}]}